gmb.io 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the [GMB website](https://gmb.io/) (the “Site”). This Privacy Policy explains the manner in which we may collect, use and disclose personal information which you provide to us. By visiting this Site or otherwise providing us with your personal information, you agree to be bound by the terms of this policy.

We want to assure you that GMB takes privacy matters very seriously and is committed to protecting your privacy. Therefore, we are providing this policy to explain our privacy practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

EFFECTIVE DATE: February 10, 2016

## COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We only collect personal information that you provide to us or that is otherwise provided to us on your behalf. You may choose to provide certain personal information in order to access or use certain features or services of the Site, such as making a purchase, requesting information, or otherwise contacting us. Such information may include your name, phone number, email address, mailing address, credit card or banking information or other information. You can always choose not to provide information, but it may limit your ability to use a particular service or feature on the Site.

By providing your personal information to us, you are authorizing us to collect, use and disclose such information in the manner outlined in this policy. Unless we advise otherwise, your information will only be used for the purposes for which it was provided or in order to contact you regarding related matters. We limit the information we collect to what we feel is necessary for those purposes.

We may periodically send you newsletters, emails or similar communications featuring sales and promotions, news about new GMB products and services, requests for your feedback, or other information we think may be of interest to you, in accordance with local law.  You may stop receiving marketing communications from us at any time by following the instructions included in the message you receive.

GMB also collects information that is sent to us automatically by your web browser. The information we receive depends upon your browser’s settings. This information typically includes your computer’s IP address, the address of the web page you were visiting when you accessed our Site, the name of the operating system installed on your computer, the name and version of the browser you are using and the date and time of your visit. We use this information primarily to create statistics that help us improve our Site and make it more compatible with the technology used by our visitors. We may link this information with your personal information as we deem necessary for our business purposes. If criminal activity is suspected, we might need to share certain information with the appropriate investigative authorities. Such information may contain visitors’ IP addresses and other information which could be used to trace and identify individuals.

So-called “cookies” and other similar technologies may be used on the Site and by third parties to collect information over time and across third party websites, to support the Site’s functionality and to improve user experience. You have the ability to set your browser to reject cookies. However, if you set your browser to reject cookies, it may affect or limit the use of certain features and functionality of this Site.

## DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

GMB will not disclose, trade, rent, sell or otherwise transfer your personal information for purposes other than as those set out herein, except with your consent or as required or permitted by law.  
GMB may disclose your personal information to third party service providers or agents who provide services to or on behalf of GMB such as, but not limited to, hosting, data management and storage services, and retention services. Either GMB or such third party service provider may use servers for such purposes located in the United States or another foreign country. Your personal information may be processed and stored in the United States or such other foreign country and the governments, courts, law enforcement and regulatory agencies of that country may be able to demand disclosure of personal information pursuant to the laws of such country.

We do not generally disclose your personal information to third parties without your consent unless required by applicable law. However, there are some situations in which we may disclose your personal information without your consent including, but not limited to:

  * with our third party service providers, as we deem necessary in connection with the services being provided to us or on our behalf;
  * in connection with a merger, sale, corporate reorganization or similar business transaction involving GMB;
  * when we are required or authorized by law to do so (for example, in response to a subpoena issued by a court);
  * or if the information is already on the public record and the disclosure is directly related to the purposes for which it was recorded on the public record.

## ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

You have a right to challenge the accuracy and completeness of your personal information and to have it corrected, as appropriate. You may also have a right to request access to your personal information and receive an accounting of how that information has been used and disclosed, subject to certain exceptions prescribed by law. If your request for access is denied, we will notify you in writing of the reason for such denial. To request access or to amend your personal information, please contact GMB in writing at PO Box 15197, Mill Creek, WA 98082 or by email at howdy@gmb.io.

## SECURITY

Security for all personal information is extremely important to us. We store your personal information securely and use encryption and/or other special procedures designed to protect the information we collect from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can ever be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, GMB cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

## USE OF THIS SITE BY MINORS

This is a commercial website intended for use by individuals that are at least 18 years old. If you are less than 18 years old, you may not use this Site without the prior permission and supervision of your legal guardian. Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at this Site from those we actually know are under the age of 13, and no part of this Site is structured to attract anyone under age 13 to provide information to us.

## TERMS OF USE

Your use of this Site and any issues relating to this policy are subject to GMB’ then-current [Terms of Use](https://gmb.io/terms/), which are located on our Site.

## PRIVACY POLICY UPDATES

We reserve the right to update or modify this policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice by posting a revised version of the policy on the Site. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you by means of a conspicuous notice on our homepage. Your use of the Site or any GMB facility following any revision to the policy constitutes your agreement that all personal information collected from or about you after the revised policy is posted will be subject to the terms and conditions of the revised policy. The date listed above indicates the most recent change or update to this policy.

## QUESTIONS OR COMMENTS

If you have questions or comments about GMB’s Online Privacy Policy, please email us at howdy@gmb.io, or write to us at:

Super 301 Inc.  
PO Box 15197  
Mill Creek  
WA 98082
